<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>RimBank (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.RimBank</packageId>
  <author>user19990313(3 more hidden)</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/RimBank</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>Update of Honey Badgers mod for RimWorld 1.1
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1107239511

[img]https://i.imgur.com/GYswkZ7.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/RimBank

- Updated to 1.1 by Bar0th
	
--- Original Description ---
&lt;size=20&gt;RimBank&lt;/size&gt;
[Core mod,must be loaded before any of its sub mods]

简体中文介绍接在英文介绍之后，请往下拉。

First let me introduce 4 authors (contributors) of this mod (Label's not wide enough XD).
user19990313(ArchAuthor,Dll parts), duduluu(Textures+Preview.png), Vaniant(Defs), WishingLaws(En translation)

It is universally known (at least on this planet), Silver serves as the currency of RimWorld. Well, the white soft metal is heavy, ugly (why -7 Tynan?) and takes up countless storage zones.

That's why RimBank has developed the Banknotes.

Item added : Banknotes
-A denomination of 1,000 Silver, which never changes
-Light and durable, suitable for saving a considerable amount of money
-Accepted by any traders, so just keep some silver for change
-Available in any purchase
-New UI , deciding how much you want to pay by banknotes
-Orbital tradeships and settlements loves banknotes! And they have many as well!
-And yes, traders can give change using Silver, so no value overflows for banknotes!
-Exchange between Silver and Banknotes with any traders! (At least traders should have enough currency for this)

Building Added : RimBank ATM Terminal
-Minifiable and relatively inexpensive
-Exchange between Silver and Banknotes with RimBank at any time! (Extra fees required)
-Various extension softwares (sub mods required)

Extra Features
-Add it to your game at any time! Opening a new save is NOT required.
-Remove it from your game at any time without corrupting your saves! (See below)

HowTo
1.Load this mod after Core.
2.So that's all.
3.When trying to remove this mod,make sure you have an ATM Terminal. Select a colonist, HOLD Shift key and right-click the terminal, then (don't release key) select "Remove all mod contents". If there are any active sub mods, please make sure all the removing commands for those sub mods have been executed.

Enjoy!

PS. The new building is in "Misc" category, and will be unlocked if you've finished the research "Microelectronics Basics".
PS2. If you get stuck while solving a payment, try to stop your mouse over icons or title - A tooltip will emerge and lead the way.
PS3. The coremod of RimBank Series (aka this mod) and all sub mods must have the same MinorVersion number. Well if you cannot figure out what I'm talking about, just ignore it, a built-in ModChecker will take charge of it.
PS4. (That was a joke in RuntimeGC)
PS5. Post any errors or bugs on my forum thread or Steam workshop page.Your effort contributes to a better mod.Thanks!





&lt;size=20&gt;RimBank 边缘银行&lt;/size&gt;
[核心mod，在本系列mod中必须第一个加载]

首先感谢本mod四位作者和贡献者（没办法，写在作者那行写不开）
user19990313（作者，dll编写），风之起灵（贴图+预览图），漆原琉华（Defs），天上掉下来个劳伦斯（中译英）

众所周知，白银是边缘世界里约定俗成的通用货币。然而这种白色柔软的金属却有很多缺点：非常笨重，占用大量储存空间，降低美观度（凭什么...）等等。

而由边缘银行发行的电子钞票，恰好是与白银并行的第二种通用货币。

加入的物品：电子钞票
-面额1000白银的电子钞票，永不贬值！
-轻便又耐磨，方便大量存储，留点碎银找零就行了
-全球通用的第二大货币体系，任何商人都会接受
-一切购买中都能使用电子钞票
-新的UI让你可以选择以何种比例在交易中使用白银和钞票
-轨道商和派系基地喜欢带大量钞票来交易！
-而且商人会用白银找零！
-和商人在钞票和白银间全额兑换！（当然对方要有足够的货币）

加入的建筑：RimBank边缘银行ATM终端
-造价适中，可以卸载！
-随时向银行在钞票和白银间兑换！（有手续费）
-丰富的扩展功能（需要安装对应的子mod）

额外特性
-可中途加入存档，无需开新档
-可中途移除，不会损坏存档（见下）

如何使用
1.加载这个mod（必须在Core之后）
2.就可以了。
3.若要中途移除该mod，请首先建立一个ATM终端，选中一个殖民者后，按住Shift键点击终端，选择“移除所有mod物品”（不放开Shift）。如果加载了其他本系列的子mod，请确保所有子mod的移除程序已经被运行过。

拿去耍吧！

PS. 新建筑ATM终端在“杂项”分类里，需要解锁“微电子科技”才能建造。
PS2. 调整支付比例的UI中隐藏着各种提示，如果你遇到了不懂的地方，试着把鼠标悬停在图标或标题上——你能看到提示框。
PS3. 所有加载的子mod必须和本mod版本相同，如果你真的搞不懂我在说啥，子mod里都会内置一个检查器，有问题只要按照指示来就行了。
PS4. （老梗了，我在RuntimeGC就玩过了）
PS5. 请将任何此mod导致的bug或冲突贴到贴吧发布页上（或者Ludeon论坛，或者Steam页面），这将使mod更加完善。谢谢！
</description>
</ModMetaData>